My name's Conan Edogawa!
اسمي إيدوغاوا كونان
High school student Shinichi was forced to take a drug that shrunk him!
أُجبر طالب الثانوية كودو شينتشي على تجرّع عقار قلص جسده
Although smaller, my mind remains that of a sharp detective!
،رغم أنّي أصبحت أصغر !لا يزال عقلي عقل متحرٍّ عظيم
Today's "MuneDoki" is the last one!
،"اليوم هو آخر عرض لشارة "موني دوكي
The alibi's just too strong! Let your heart beat to the case!
!حجّة الغياب قويّة جدّاً !دع نبضات قلبك تتسارع مع القضية
There's always only one truth!
!الحقيقة واحدة دوماً
Now I see why it's a five-star hotel!
!كما تتوقع من فندق خمس نجوم
This is going to be great, Conan-kun!
سيكون هذا مثيراً، صحيح يا كونان-كن؟
Yeah...
...أ-أجل
You kids are way too spoiled...
...لذا لا يصلح الأطفال المدللون لـ
You're only here because the restaurant's on the way, got that!
أنتما هنا لأنّ المطعم في مكان عملي فقط، واضح؟
Yes, we know!
!أجل، نعرف
Say, isn't that the lawyer who wants to hire you?
أليس ذلك المُحامي الذي يريد تعيينك؟
Yep, that's him! Mr. Tatsumi!
أجل، إنّه هو. المُحامي تاتسومي
Your great detective work is highly admired,
تحريّاتك العظيمة محلّ استقبالٍ حسن
even within our judicial circles!
حتى ضمن دوائرنا القانونية يا موري-سان
No, my work doesn't begin to compare to yours...
كلا، ليست شيئاً مقارنةً بجهودك
All of my groups know about you too! It's true!
!لا أحد في دوائرنا يجهلك أيضاً! صدقاً
Having your office in this posh hotel is really impressive!
اختيارك لمكتبك في هذا الفندق الراقي يليق بك حقّاً
Tricks like this are necessary when dealing with corporations.
تحتاج لحيل المظاهر عند التعامل مع الشركات الكبيرة
So he's a popular lawyer who advises a number of large corporations...
أي أنّه مُحامٍ واسع الشعبية تستشيره كبار الشركات
Wow!
!مُذهل
What would you like to drink?
ماذا تشربون؟
I'll have coffee.
سأشرب قهوة
These two don't need anything; I'll kick them out soon.
لا يحتاج هذان شيئاً، سأخرجهما فوراً
There's no need to hurry.
لا داعي للعجلة
Take your time and relax.
خذ وقتك واسترخ
Hello? Room service, please.
مرحباً؟ خدمة الغرف من فضلك
If there's no reason to hurry, then why's he so fixated on the time?
إذا لم يكن هناك داعٍ للعجلة فلمَ يشغله الوقت؟
Excuse me while I use the restroom.
اعذروني، سأذهب للحمام
Sorry, but could someone answer that for me?
آسف، هلّا أجبتم على الهاتف؟
It automatically records calls!
!إنّه يسجل المكالمات آلياً
Hello?
مرحباً؟
Oh? You're not my husband...
ماذا؟ لستَ زوجي
Um, who may I ask is calling?
المعذرة، من تكونين؟
Who do you think? Mrs. Tatsumi, of course.
من أكون؟ أنا زوجة تاتسومي بالطبع
Oops.
كلا
What is that?
ما هذا؟
Little boy?
مرحباً يا فتى
Could you put my husband on?
هلّا أعطيت السمّاعة لزوجي؟
Yes, just a minute--
...حاضر، انتظري قليلاً
Mr. Lawyer, it's your wife...
سيّدي المحامي، إنّها زوجتك
She never learns...
لا حلّ معها
It's me. I have guests right now.
إنه أنا، لديّ ضيوف الآن
We can talk later.
لنؤجل الكلام لاحقاً
Sorry. Now, about my job.
أعتذر، بخصوص طلبي الآن
Before that... Ran, Conan.
قبل ذلك... ران، كونان
Right!
أجل
Let's go, Conan-kun.
لنذهب يا كونان-كن
There's a tea lounge in the lobby.
توجد حجرة شاي في صالة الانتظار
Tell them my room number and order whatever you'd like.
أعطياهم رقم الغرفة واطلبا ما شئتما
Thank you!
!نستأذن
I'd like you to investigate possible infidelity.
أودّ منك أن تتحرّى عن خيانة
Of my wife, Kazumi.
خيانة زوجتي كازومي
It's almost been an hour...
مضت ساعة تقريباً
Here he comes.
أتى العمّ
Dad!
!أبي
Oh, there you are.
أنتما هنا
That took long. Is it a hard job?
أخذتَ وقتاً، أكان عملاً صعباً؟
No, not exactly...
...حسناً، بخصوص ذلك
Is something the matter?
أهناك خطبٌ ما؟
He just wouldn't stop babbling about how he'd like
كان يقول: "ربما حريّ بي أن أثق بزوجتي مُجدداً" وما شابه
to trust his wife again, so it took longer than I expected.
لم يكن صارماً بخلاف ما يبدو عليه، فأطلنا
So he's investigating the wife's infidelity...
يتحرّى خيانة الزوجة إذاً
Anyway, I took the case.
قبلت القضيّة بأيّ حال
So let's go eat at this restaurant of yours.
لنذهب ونأكل في المطعم الذي تكلمتِ عنه
Hurray!
!رائع
Which is what I'd like to say, but this is the underground parking garage!
!أريد قول ذلك، لكننا عند مواقف السيارات السفلية يا أبي
The restaurant is up there!
!المطعم في الأعلى
Were you even being serious about going?!
أكنتَ تنوي الذهاب له حتّى؟
Mr. Tatsumi...
المُحامي تاتسومي؟
Conan! Let's go!
!هيّا بنا يا كونان
Coming!
!حاضر
I think I drank too much...
لعلّي أفرطت في الشرب
A police car. I wonder what for?
سيّارة شرطة، ماذا حصل يا ترى؟
What a huge mansion!
!يا للمنزل الكبير
So this is Mr. Tatsumi's house...
هذا منزل المحامي تاتسومي إذاً
Lawyers must really make a lot...
يجني المُحامون مالاً كثيراً حقاً
Inspector Megure. I brought Detective Mori.
حضرة المفتش ميغوري، أحضرتُ المتحرّي موري
Oh! Thanks for coming, Mori-kun!
شكراً على قدومك يا موري-كن
Well, come have a look.
تعال وانظر
You two wait there.
انتظرا عندكما
Isn't that's Mr. Tatsumi's wife?
تلك زوجة المحامي تاتسومي، صحيح؟
Yes. Kazumi-san. Twenty-seven years old.
أجل، كازومي-سان، 27 عاماً
The cause of death was suffocation by strangulation.
كان سبب الوفاة الخنق حتّى الموت
There's no question this was a murder.
لا شكّ أنها كانت جريمة قتل
A staple!
دبّوس
What's this doing here?
لمَ يوجد هنا؟
Alright, you!
!أنت
What do you think you're doin'?!
!ما الذي تفعله؟
Now, now, Mori-kun.
رويدك يا موري-كن
All three of your testimonies are needed this time.
نحتاج شهاداتكم جميعاً هذه المرّة
Testimonies?
شهادات؟
Yes, it's true that my wife and I didn't get along.
أجل، لم تكن علاقتي وزوجتي حسنةً بالفعل
That's why I hired Mori-san to check up on her...
لذا طلبتُ من موري-سان التحرّي عنها
Inspector. What was the estimated time of death?
حضرة المفتش، ما وقت الوفاة المقدّر؟
We won't know the details until the autopsy,
لا نعرف التفاصيل حتى يتمّ التشريح
but judging from the state of rigor mortis, I'd say between 2:00 and 3:00 p.m.
لكن بناءً على تصلّب الجثّة، فأرجح أنّه كان بين الثانية والثالثة مساءً
That's when we were--
...كنّا وقتها
Yeah, that's when we were at the hotel.
أجل، في الفندق
Now I get it.
فهمت
So they called us here to confirm his alibi...
لذا استدعانا لإثبات حجّة غيابه
I parted with Mori-san and left the hotel.
انفصلتُ عن موري-سان وغادرت الفندق
I finished researching my next case, and then when I came home, my wife was--
،أنهيتُ البحث المتعلّق بجلسة المحاكمة المقبلة ...وعندما رجعت للبيت وجدت زوجتي
--as you saw...
كما رأيتم
Mori-kun. You're certain you were with Mr. Tatsumi
موري-كن، أتؤكد بأنّك كنت رفقة المحامي تاتسومي
between 2:00 and 3:00?
بين الثانية والثالثة؟
Yes. I'm certain.
أجل، لا شكّ في ذلك
He only disappeared from my sight once,
غاب عن ناظري مرّةً فقط
and that was for only a minute.
ولم يدم ذلك لأكثر من دقيقة
Oh yes, the phone rang then...
...صحيح، رنّ الهاتف وقتها
Yeah! They said, "I'm Mrs. Tatsumi, of course!"
"أجل، قالت "أنا زوجة تاتسومي بالطبع
Which means she was still alive at that time?
ما يعني أنّها كانت حيّةً في ذاك الوقت؟
The tape of that conversation should still be in the phone at the hotel!
يوجد تسجيل لتلك المحادثة في هاتف الفندق كما أظن
Really?! May we borrow this tape?
حقاً؟ أيمكننا استعارة ذاك التسجيل؟
Of course. That's fine with me.
أجل، لا أمانع
At any rate, Tatsumi-sensei was with me
بأيّ حال، كان تاتسومي سينسي معي
between 2:00 and 3:00; his alibi is airtight.
بين الثانية والثالثة فحجّة غيابه مطبقة
And besides, the hotel is 10 kilometers from his home.
كما يبعد الفندق 10 كيلومترات تقريباً عن منزله
Lawyer's Wife Murdered
مقتل زوجة المحامي
"Lawyer's wife murdered.
،جريمة قتل زوجة المحامي"
The focus of the investigation is on the victim's associate?"
"تركيز التحقيق على علاقة الضحيّة الحميمة؟
She was having an affair.
أي خيانة زوجية
Mr. Tatsumi's wife was killed by her other lover?!
قُتلت زوجة المحامي تاتسومي على يد عشيقها؟
Judging from the scene of the crime, it wasn't a robbery.
لم تكن هناك آثار سرقة في مسرح الجريمة
Our testimonies cleared Tatsumi-sensei of all suspicion.
وأبرأت شهاداتنا تاتسومي سينسي من الشبهة
Which narrows it down.
مما يقلّص الاحتمالات
Damn it! I lost that case thanks to whoever killed her!
!تبّاً! ذلك جانباً، تبخرت القضيّة بسبب ذاك المجرم
That makes me mad!
!دمي يغلي
Something's not right.
غريب
There are too many things about this case that bother me!
توجد أشياء كثيرة تحيّرني في هذه القضية
Why was it necessary to put the body in the bathtub?
لمَ تكبّد القاتل عناء وضع الجثّة في حوض الاستحمام؟
What was that staple for?
وما كان مغزى ذاك الدبّوس؟
The way Mr. Tatsumi stalled the old man for an hour...
ومماطلة المحامي تاتسومي للعمّ ساعةً كاملة
Why was he so fixated on the time?
لمَ كان يشغله الوقت لذاك الحدّ؟
Was it mere coincidence that he had someone else pick up the phone?
أكان ردّ شخص غيره على الهاتف محض مصادفة؟
What did he put in the car trunk?
ما الذي وضعه في صندوق سيّارته؟
I guess all the questions start from the hotel!
!مُنطلق كلّ تلك الأسئلة هو الفندق
Was that Conan-kun?
أكان ذلك كونان-كن؟
Conan-kun! Where are you going?
كونان-كن! أين تذهب؟
I'll be back in time!
!سأرجع في الوقت
This is Mr. Tatsumi's office.
هذا مكتب المحامي تاتسومي
The guest elevator is down there.
ومصعد الضيوف هناك
Similarly, the employee elevator is over there.
ومصعد العاملين هناك من ناحية
The emergency exit is far, too.
مخرج الطوارئ بعيد أيضاً
What's that?
ما ذاك؟
It's a laundry chute...
...إنّها قناة غسيل
The staple!
!الدبّوس
That's it!
!ذاك هو
As always,
،كالعادة
I've prepared the room next to my office, so please make yourselves at home.
حضّرتُ الغرفة بجوار مكتبي فخذوا راحتكم
The room next to his office? As always?
الغرفة بجوار مكتبه؟ كالعادة؟
This is--
...هذا
Where is it coming from?!
من أين يأتي؟
From here.
هنا
So that's what this is...
...هذا هو إذاً
They have a music box instead of an alarm clock buzzer!
لديهم صندوق موسيقيّ بدل طنّان ساعة التنبيه
No, I'm exploring!
!كلا، أنا أستكشف
Or are you getting into trouble?
أم تعبث بالأحرى؟
That reminds me--
...ذاك الوقت أيضاً
--the music box stopped during the phone call!
توقف الصندوق الموسيقي أثناء الاتّصال
What a rare alarm clock!
يا لساعة التنبيه الغريبة
Do any other rooms have one?
أتوجد في بقية الغرف مثلها؟
Of course. All the rooms do.
بالطبع، كلّ الغرف
They each have a real music box hooked up to a timer.
بها صندوق موسيقيّ حقيقيّ موصول بمؤقت
I've finally found it!
!وجدتُه أخيراً
Definitive proof that Mr. Tatsumi killed her!
!الدليل الدامغ ليُدين المحامي تاتسومي
You're late!
!تأخّرت
Look how late you are!
!تأخّرت كثيراً
You knew we were going somewhere! Where were you?!
!كنت تعرف أنّنا سنذهب لمكانٍ ما! أين كنت؟
Where's the old man?
أين العمّ؟
He already left!
سبقنا
You did this! You killed Kazumi!
!أنت الفاعل! أنت من قتل كازومي
I'm with the police. What's going on here?
أنا مع الشرطة، ما الذي يجري؟
Who are you?
من أنت؟
Hirose. I'm a design engineer.
هيروسي، مهندس تصميم
I'm the man you're looking for.
أنا الرجل الذي تبحثون عنه
I had an affair with Kazumi, the victim.
كانت بيني والضحيّة كازومي علاقة
What?!
ماذا؟
But I didn't kill her! Why would I?!
لكنّي لم أقتلها، لمَ عساي أن أفعل؟
She was about to divorce this guy
فقد كانت على وشك تطليق هذا الرجل
and marry me!
!والزواج بي
Oh, that's news to me.
هذا كلامٌ جديد عليّ
Don't play dumb!
!لا تتظاهر بالغباء
You knew!
!كنتَ تعرف
He knew?
كان يعرف؟
Assuming I had known, why would I kill her?
بافتراض أنّي كنت أعرف، لمَ قد أقتلها؟
As a lawyer, I've heard about scores of cases
،كما مرّت عليّ أكوام قضايا خيانات زوجية
in which affairs led to murder.
قادت لجرائم قتل في عملي كمحامٍ
Why, you!
!أيّها الوغد
And besides, I have an alibi.
كما لديّ حجّة غياب
I couldn't possibly have killed her.
يستحيل أنّي قتلتها
Isn't that right, Mori-san?
أليس ذلك صحيحاً يا موري-سان؟
Yes, I can vouch for him.
أجل، أنا أشهد
Hirose-kun, was it?
اسمك هيروسي-كن؟
So how about yourself?
ماذا عنك إذاً؟
What's your alibi?
ما حجّة غيابك؟
Where were you between 2:00 and 3:00 p.m.
أين كنت بين الثانية والثالثة مساءً يوم مقتلها؟
I was--
...كـ-كنت
Where were you?
أين كنت؟
I was tricked!
لقد خُدعت
Tricked?!
خُدعت؟
I came here because of Kazumi's letter...
أتيت هنا بسبب رسالة كازومي
Here.
هذه
"I'll be waiting for you at home at 2:30.
".سأنتظرك في المنزل عند الثانية والنصف. كازومي"
But she wasn't home.
لكنّها لم تكن موجودة
I rang the doorbell, but nobody answered, so I left!
ضغطتُ على الجرس لكن لم يجب أحد، فغادرت
This is really hard to believe,
يصعب التصديق بما أنّك كنت حاضراً في مسرح الجريمة وقت وقوعها
Anyone can easily make something like this!
!يمكن لأيّ أحد تزييف رسالة كهذه ببساطة
You're a sore loser!
!لا تعرف الاستسلام
It's clear that you're the killer!
!من الجليّ أنّك القاتل
Inspector. Take him in.
سيّدي المفتش، اعتقله
He ruined my case!
!لقد بخّر قضيّتي
Ruined?
بخّرها؟
You got it all wrong!
أ-أخطأت
He always does!
يفعل دائماً
Hirose-san. I'd like you to come down to the station.
هيروسي-سان، هلّا رافقتنا للمركز؟
Sorry, old man!
!آسف يا عمّ
Are you all right?
أأنت بخير؟
I'm fine, thanks.
أنا بخير، شكراً
No! It wasn't me!
!كلا! لم يكن أنا
He's right.
معه حق
The real sore loser isn't Hirose-san-- it's you, Tatsumi-sensei!
،من لا يعرف الاستسلام ليس هيروسي-سان !بل أنت يا تاتسومي سينسي
What do you mean, Mori-kun?
ما قصدك يا موري-كن؟
Are you saying Mr. Tatsumi is the killer?
هل المحامي تاتسومي هو القاتل؟
Precisely.
بالضبط
Really now, this is absurd.
...كنتُ أفكّر بما الذي قد تقوله
This will tarnish your name as a great detective, Mori-san!
ستلطّخ اسمك اللامع يا موري-سان
I could say the exact same thing to you, Mr. Tatsumi.
يمكنني ردّ كلامك لك حضرة المحامي
It truly was an impressive trick of utilizing blind spots.
كانت حيلةً مُبهرة بحق باستعمال النقاط العمياء
You had me completely fooled.
خدعتني تماماً
The place a body is found doesn't necessarily equate
مكان العثور على الجثّة لا يعني بالضرورة أنّه مكان الجريمة
In other words, the murder didn't take place here at your home,
أي أنّ الجريمة لم تقع في منزلك
but at the hotel!
بل في الفندق
No way!
!مُحال
What are you talking about?!
!ما-ما الذي تقوله؟
Mori-kun!
موري-كن، صوت المرأة المسجّل في المكالمة
Yes, of course it was her.
أجل، كان صوتها بالطبع
Because she called from the room next to Tatsumi-sensei's office,
لأنّها اتّصلت من الغرفة المجاورة لمكتب تاتسومي سينسي
which he had rented.
التي استأجرتها
Come again?!
!ماذا؟
The room next door?!
الغرفة المجاورة؟
On that day, Tatsumi-sensei
...في ذاك اليوم، جعل تاتسومي سينسي
made his wife wait in the guest room that he always uses for clients.
زوجته تنتظر في غرفة الضيوف التي يبقيها لعملائه دوماً
He then had her call the hotel at a predetermined time
بهاتف خلوي
He made someone else answer the unconnected call.
وجعل شخصاً غيره يجيب على الاتّصال
Hello?
مرحباً؟
Because nobody would ever suspect that the caller was in the very next room.
لأنّه لن يخطر ببال أحد أنّ المتصل كان في الغرفة المجاورة
Immediately after his business with me ended,
،بعد نهاية اجتماعنا
he went next door and killed his wife.
ذهب للغرفة المجاورة وقتل زوجته
He put the body in a laundry basket
ثمّ وضع الجثّة في سلّة غسيل
and dropped it down a nearby laundry chute.
وأسقطها في قناة الغسيل بالقرب
That was the hotel employees' break time
كان ذلك وقت راحة الموظفين
so there wasn't a soul to be found, was there, Tatsumi-sensei?
فلم يكن هناك أيّ شخص في الجوار، صحيح يا تاتسومي سينسي؟
However, the bag with the body was stapled.
لكنّ الكيس الذي احتوى الجثة قد دُبّس
Stapled with a cleaning tag.
بالدبوس الخاص بتثبيت بطاقات التنظيف
That was the staple found in the bathroom, Inspector Megure.
وكان ذاك الدبّوس الذي وجدناه في الحمّام سيّدي المفتش
Now that you mention it...
...بذكرك ذلك
But why was the body in the bathtub?
لكن لمَ كانت الجثّة في حوض الاستحمام؟
His plan probably started when he realized
بدأت خطّته غالباً عندما أدرك
that the trunk and the bathtub are about the same size.
أنّ حجم صندوق السيارة وحوض الاستحمام متطابق تقريباً
The body would stiffen,
،ستتصلّب الجثّة
so he couldn't just toss it in the house.
فلم يمكنه رميها في المنزل فحسب
Then he pointed the finger at Hirose-san who was lured here by the fake letter,
ثمّ وجه إصبع الاتّهام نحو هيروسي-سان الذي اُستدرج إلى هنا برسالة مزيّفة
and then he escaped suspicion by having me vouch for him.
ويهرب بعدها من الشبهة بشهادتي له
It really was quite impressive.
كانت خطّة متقنة بحق
You disappoint me. You're a lousy detective.
خيّبت أملي، يا للمتحرّي الفاشل
Where is your proof that I killed her?
ما دليلك على أنّي قتلتها؟
No court of law could make me stand trial like this.
لن أدخل محاكمةً هكذا، ولن يصدر أيّ أمر اعتقال حتّى
He's right, Mori-kun!
!معه حقّ يا موري-كن
I do have proof.
الدليل موجود
Inspector. There's something I'd like you to get right away.
سيّدي المفتش، هناك شيء أريدك أن تجلبه فوراً
The tape of the phone call...
...شريط تسجيل المكالمة
Is that all you need, Mori-kun?
هذا كلّ ما تحتاجه يا موري-كن؟
The tape of my wife on the phone?
تسجيل مكالمة زوجتي؟
What do you want with that?!
ماذا تريد به؟
Play it, if you would.
شغّله رجاءً
Hello?
مرحباً؟
Oh? You're not my husband...
...ماذا؟ لست زوجي
Um, who may I ask is calling?
المعذرة، من تكونين؟
Who do you think? Mrs. Tatsumi, of course.
من أكون؟ أنا زوجة تاتسومي بالطبع
What's this?!
ما-ما هذا؟
A music box?
صندوق موسيقي؟
Shh! Quiet!
!صه! صمتاً
Oops.
كلا
Little boy?
مرحباً يا فتى، هلّا أعطيت السمّاعة لزوجي؟
Yes, just a minute--
...حاضر، انتظري قليلاً
That's enough.
يكفي
Now do you see?
هل فهمتم؟
That hotel uses this music box in place of alarm clock buzzers.
يستعمل ذاك الفندق هذا الصندوق الموسيقيّ مكان طنان ساعة التنبيه
In other words, your wife had set the alarm
أي أنّ زوجتك كانت قد ضبطت المؤقت
but forgot to turn it off when making the call.
لكن نسيت إطفاءه عند إجراء المكالمة
Sorry, but music boxes like this can be found anywhere.
تجد هذه الصناديق الموسيقية في كلّ مكان للأسف
It doesn't prove a thing.
لن تنفع دليلاً
Inspector.
سيدي المفتش، أتوجد أيّ صناديق موسيقية في موقع اكتشاف الجثة؟
No, none at all.
كلا، مُطلقاً
The killer could have run off with it for whatever reason.
يمكن أنّ القاتل أخذه معه لسببٍ ما
Unlikely.
غير مُرجّح
And why's that?
ولمَ ذلك؟
Conan. The tape.
كونان، الشريط
Right!
!حاضر
Here!
هاك. هذا تسجيلٌ للصندوق الموسيقي في الغرفة بجوار مكتب المحامي تاتسومي
Give it a listen.
حسنٌ، استمعوا له
It's missing a note!
!تنقصه نغمة
That's right. The music box in the next room over
صحيح، الصندوق الموسيقي في الغرفة المجاورة
is probably missing either a cylinder pin or a tooth!
ينقصه دبّوس، أو يعاني مشط الاهتزاز خللاً
In other words, it's the only music box like it in the world, Tatsumi-sensei!
ما يعني أنّه صندوق موسيقي لا مثيل له في العالم يا تاتسومي سينسي
Now then, let's hear the phone recording one more time.
إذاً، هل نعيد الاستماع لتسجيل المكالمة؟
It would be a waste of time.
سيكون تضييعاً للوقت
To think a lawyer would be blackmailed by his own wife...
من كان ليتصوّر تعرّض مُحامٍ للابتزاز من قِبل زوجته؟
Blackmailed? By your wife?
ابتزاز؟ من زوجتك؟
She demanded 200 million.
طلبت 200 مليون
Two hundred million?!
!مئتي مليون؟
It took skill to get where I am today.
تطلّب وصولي للشهرة والمكانة التي أملكهما مهارةً كبيرة
But because of my position, I'm often privy to corporate secrets and the like.
لكن بسبب موضعي، أطّلع على أسرار الشركات والمعلومات الداخلية كثيراً
I never made any demands,
،حتّى دون طلبي
but a lot of extra money was added to my counsel fees.
يقدمون لي مبلغاً إضافياً فوق أجري
Some of it was illegal, to be more precise.
أي مال غير قانونيّ
Kazumi found out about this.
اكتشفت كازومي ذلك
I'll keep quiet if you give me 200 million--
سأبقى صامتةً إن أعطيتني 200 مليون
It's not that much when you consider you can keep your reputation.
ليس شيئاً يُذكر مقارنة باحتفاظك بسمعتك
But then she got involved with that designer...
...لكن بعدها دخلت في علاقة مع ذاك المُصمم
I couldn't let her get away with it.
لم أستطع تركها تفلت بذلك، ذاك ما فكّرتُ به
"I'll do what you want, but on one condition.
سأفعل ما تريدين، لكن بشرط واحد"
Call me at the specified time or else I won't pay the 200 million!"
اتّصلي بي في الوقت المحدد وإلّا "لن أدفع المئتي مليون
She agreed without a single question.
وافقتْ على ذلك دون أيّ سؤال
She would get 200 million and her man!
كانت ستحصل على 200 مليون كما عشيقها
It was only natural.
ذلك طبيعيّ
But you shouldn't have made her call.
لكن كان عليك ألّا تجعلها تجري الاتصال
You had the call recorded automatically,
سجّلته آلياً
but you should've listened to it again before giving it to the police.
لكن كان حريّ بك الاستماع له قبل الموافقة على تسليمه للشرطة
Your trick to pull off the perfect crime actually wound up proving your guilt.
حيلتك لتنفيذ الجريمة الكاملة انقلبت عليك بإدانتك
I gambled with myself.
راهنتُ على نفسي
No matter how good the lawyer, the moment of truth is always a gamble.
مهما برع المحامي فلحظة الحقيقة تبقى رهاناً
Until now, I'd never once lost that bet.
لم يسبق وخسرتُ بذاك الرهان حتّى الآن
You may be a good lawyer, but you were a poor criminal.
قد تكون مُحامياً متفوقاً، لكنّك مجرم مبتدئ
That's how it is, sir.
هكذا الأمر يا سينسي
Inspector!
!حضرة المفتش
Good work, Mori-kun.
عملٌ ممتاز يا موري-كن
Despite being tricked and taken advantage of.
رغم تعرّضك للخداع والاستغلال
Hope to work with you again.
أتطلّع للعمل معك مُجدداً
Oh, uh, same here...
أ-أجل، يسرّني ذلك
Tricked? Who? By who?
خداع؟ من؟ وممن؟
Oh, well!
!لا يهم
Gimme a break.
...يا إلهي
Now his reputation keeps getting better and better...
سمعته الآن تتحسن أكثر فأكثر
It was definitely Matsuo-san who did this!
!كان المجرم ماتسو-سان بلا شك
But how did he go from the studio and back in four minutes?!
لكن كيف ذهب ورجع من الاستوديو في 4 دقائق؟
Aha! I've finally found the secret path!
!فهمت! وجدتُ الطريق السرّي أخيراً
I wouldn't want the criminal to leave
لا يمكنك أن تغادر
when the logic show's just about to begin...
بينما يوشك برنامجي للتحرّي على البدء
...Takashi Matsuo-san!
!خصوصاً أنّك القاتل يا ماتسو تاكاشي-سان
On the next Conan--
في الحلقة القادمة من كونان
The TV Station Murder Case.
جريمة قتل محطّة التلفاز
Next Conan's Hint:
تلميح الحلقة القادمة
Bloody window.
نافذة